Annette Kolodny papers, 1968-[ongoing]
University of Arizona Libraries, Special Collections
- Series 4: Legal, 1970-1984
  - Subseries 1: Correspondence, ca. 1970-1983
    - Correspondence--Legal (Lawyer/Client), March 14, 1980-August 13, 1980 (Box 26, Folder 6)
    - Correspondence--Legal (Lawyer/Client), August 16, 1980-September 22, 1980 (Box 26, Folder 7)
    - Correspondence--Legal (Lawyer/Client), September 23, 1980-January 21, 1982 (Box 26, Folder 8)
    - Correspondence--NH Commission and Findings, February, 1975-September, 1975 (Box 26, Folder 9)
    - Correspondence--NH Commission and Findings, September 12, 1975-April 27, 1977 (Box 26, Folder 10)
    - Correspondence--Promotion, 1974-1975 (Box 27, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence--Promotion, 1974-1975 (Box 27, Folder 2)
    - Correspondence--Promotion, 1975-1976 (Box 27, Folder 3)
    - Correspondence--Promotion & Tenure (Box 27, Folder 4)
    - Correspondence--Student correspondence, 1976-1978 (Box 27, Folder 5)
    - Correspondence--Support (Box 27, Folder 6)
    - Correspondence--University of New Hampshire, 1973-1975 (Box 27, Folder 7)
    - Correspondence--University of New Hampshire, 1976 (Box 27, Folder 8)
    - Correspondence--University of New Hampshire, March, 1976-April, 1976 (Box 27, Folder 9)
    - Correspondence--University of New Hampshire, April, 1976-July, 1976 (Box 27, Folder 10)
  - Subseries 2: Depositions, 1977-1980
    - Depositions--Carnicelli, Thomas, 1979 (Box 28, Folder 1)
    - Depositions--Dawson, Carl, 1979 (Box 28, Folder 2)
    - Depositions--Hapgood, Robert D., August 23, 1977 (Box 28, Folder 3)
    - Depositions--Hapgood, Robert D., August 31, 1977 (Box 28, Folder 4)
    - Depositions--Hapgood, Robert D., with comments, August 23, 1977 (Box 28, Folder 5)
    - Depositions--Hapgood, Robert D., exhibits, 1977 (Box 28, Folder 6)
    - Depositions--Kolodny, Annette, part 1 volume 1, August 16, 1978 (Box 28, Folder 7)
    - Depositions--Kolodny, Annette, part 2 volume 1, August 16, 1978 (Box 29, Folder 1)
    - Depositions--Kolodny, Annette, part 1 volume 2, September 13, 1978 (Box 29, Folder 2)
    - Depositions--Kolodny, Annette, part 2 volume 2, September 13, 1978 (Box 29, Folder 3)
    - Depositions--Kolodny, Annette, corrections (Box 29, Folder 4)
    - Depositions--Murray, Donald M., 1980 (Box 29, Folder 5)
    - Depositions--Murray, Donald M., exhibits, 1980 (Box 29, Folder 6)
    - Depositions--Smith, Mark, exhibits (Box 29, Folder 7)
    - Depositions--Smith, Mark October 17, 1979-January 9, 1980 (Box 29, Folder 8)
  - Subseries 3: Legal Fund, ca.1975-1980
    - Legal Fund--Appeal Letters (Box 30, Folder 1)
    - Legal Fund--Appeal Letters, "Legal Fund for Annette Kolodny," (Box 30, Folder 2)
    - Legal Fund--Attorney Fees (Box 30, Folder 3)
    - Legal Fund--Bank Statements, (checking), December 1977-January 1981 (Box 30, Folder 4)
    - Legal Fund--Bank Statements (savings), 1979-1977 (Box 30, Folder 5)
    - Legal Fund--Checks (Box 30, Folder 6)
    - Legal Fund--Correspondence (support), 1978 (Box 30, Folder 7)
    - Legal Fund--Correspondence (support), 1978 (Box 30, Folder 8)
    - Legal Fund--Correspondence (support), 1978 (Box 30, Folder 9)
    - Legal Fund--Legal Expenses (Box 30, Folder 10)
    - Legal Fund--Legal Fund, 1975-1978 (Box 30, Folder 11)
    - Legal Fund--Legal Fund (Box 30, Folder 12)
    - Legal Fund--Legal Fund, 1980 (Box 30, Folder 13)
    - Legal Fund--Press Releases (Box 30, Folder 14)
  - Subseries 4: News Clippings and Papers, 1970-1982
    - News Clippings, 1970-1974 (Box 31, Folder 1)
    - News Clippings, 1975 (Box 31, Folder 2)
    - News Clippings, 1976 (Box 31, Folder 3)
    - News Clippings, 1977 (Box 31, Folder 4)
    - News Clippings, 1978 (Box 31, Folder 5)
    - News Clippings, 1979 (Box 31, Folder 6)
    - News Clippings, 1980 (Box 31, Folder 7)
    - News Clippings (Box 31, Folder 8)
    - Paper: Abel, Emily "Collective Protest & the Meritocracy..," 1980 (Box 31, Folder 9)
    - Paper: "Resolving Sex Discrimination Grievances on Campus," 1982 (Box 31, Folder 10)
    - Paper: "Service at UNH," (Box 31, Folder 11)
    - Paper: "Women of the Year," 1978 (Box 31, Folder 12)
  - Subseries 5: Promotion & Tenure, 1973-1979
    - Promotion & Tenure--Promotion/Tenure file, part 1, 1976 (Box 32, Folder 1)
    - Promotion & Tenure--Promotion/Tenure file, part 2, 1975-1976 (Box 32, Folder 2)
    - Promotion & Tenure--Promotion File, Appendix A, 1975-1976 (Box 32, Folder 3)
    - Promotion & Tenure--Promotion File, Appendix A, 1975-1976 (Box 32, Folder 4)
    - Promotion & Tenure--Promotion File, Appendix B, 1976-1977 (Box 32, Folder 5)
    - Promotion & Tenure--Promotion File, Appendix C, 1977-1978 (Box 32, Folder 6)
    - Promotion & Tenure--Promotion File, Appendix C, 1977-1978 (Box 32, Folder 7)
    - Promotion & Tenure--Promotion File, Appendix D, 1973-1978 (Box 32, Folder 8)
    - Promotion & Tenure--University guidelines for promotion and tenure (Box 32, Folder 9)
    - Promotion & Tenure--Promotion standards, 1975-1976 (Box 32, Folder 10)
    - Promotion & Tenure--Tenure and Promotion Committee, 1979 (Box 32, Folder 11)
    - Promotion & Tenure--Tenure and Promotion Committee--Pre-employment documents, 1974 (Box 33, Folder 1)
    - Promotion & Tenure--Tenure and Promotion Committee--first promotion review, 1974 (Box 33, Folder 2)
    - Promotion & Tenure--Tenure and Promotion Committee--first promotion review, 1975 (Box 33, Folder 3)
    - Promotion & Tenure--Tenure and Promotion Committee--second promotion review, 1975 (Box 33, Folder 4)
    - Promotion & Tenure--Tenure and Promotion Committee--second promotion review, January, 1976 (Box 33, Folder 5)
    - Promotion & Tenure--Tenure and Promotion Committee--second promotion review, April-July, 1976 (Box 33, Folder 6)
    - Promotion & Tenure--Tenure and Promotion Committee--third promotion review, 1976 (Box 33, Folder 7)
    - Promotion & Tenure--Tenure and Promotion Committee--third promotion review, 1977 (Box 33, Folder 8)
    - Promotion & Tenure--Kolodny review file, 1975-1976 (Box 34, Folder 1)
    - Promotion & Tenure--Tenure, 1976-1977 (Box 34, Folder 2)
    - Promotion & Tenure--Tenure, 1977-1978 (Box 34, Folder 3)
    - Promotion & Tenure--Tenure review, 1977-1978 (Box 34, Folder 4)
    - Promotion & Tenure--Tenure review, 1977-1978 (Box 34, Folder 5)
    - Promotion & Tenure--Tenure review, 1977-1978 (Box 34, Folder 6)
    - Promotion & Tenure--Tenure review, 1977-1978 (Box 34, Folder 7)
    - Promotion & Tenure--Tenure review, Spitz, Alan, 1977-1978 (Box 34, Folder 8)
  - Sub-series 6: Student evaluations, 1974-1977
    - Student Evaluations--Survey of American Literature, 1974-1975 (Box 35, Folder 1)
    - Student Evaluations--Survey of American Literature, 1974-1975 (Box 35, Folder 2)
    - Student Evaluations--Puritanism & Enlightenment in America, 1974-1975 (Box 35, Folder 3)
    - Student Evaluations--Survey of American Literature, 1976-1977 (Box 35, Folder 4)
    - Student Evaluations--Survey of American Literature, 1976-1977 (Box 35, Folder 5)
    - Student Evaluations--20th Century Women Writers, 1976-1977 (Box 35, Folder 6)
    - Student Evaluations--Survey of American Literature, 1976-1977 (Box 35, Folder 7)
    - Student Evaluations--American Women Writers & Feminist Criticism, 1976-1977 (Box 35, Folder 8)
  - Subseries 7: Trial Material ca.1968-1980
    - Trial Material--Background information, 1972-1980 (Box 36, Folder 1)
    - Trial Material--Certificate of Service, September 27, 1978 (Box 36, Folder 2)
    - Trial Material--Cody Report, 1974-1975 (Box 36, Folder 3)
    - Trial Material--Cody Report--related documents, 1974-1975 (Box 36, Folder 4)
    - Trial Material--Complaint (original), 1975-1976 (Box 36, Folder 5)
    - Trial Material--Contract (Box 36, Folder 6)
    - Trial Material--Corroboratory Material (Box 36, Folder 7)
    - Trial Material--Corroboratory Material (Box 36, Folder 8)
    - Trial Material--Corroboratory Material (Box 36, Folder 9)
    - Trial Material--Corroboratory Material (Box 37, Folder 1)
    - Trial Material--Corroboratory Material (Box 37, Folder 2)
    - Trial Material--Curriculum review, 1974-1980 (Box 37, Folder 3)
    - Trial Material--Curriculum vita, resume, 1975-1978 (Box 37, Folder 4)
    - Trial Material--Dawson, Carl (Box 37, Folder 5)
    - Trial Material--Department, English (Box 37, Folder 6)
    - Trial Material--Department, English (Box 37, Folder 7)
    - Trial Material--Documents provided by defendant, 1974 (Box 37, Folder 8)
    - Trial Material--Documents provided by defendant, 1974 (Box 37, Folder 9)
    - Trial Material--Documents provided by defendant, 1974 (Box 37, Folder 10)
    - Trial Material--Experts (defense), 1978 (Box 37, Folder 11)
    - Trial Material--Experts (defense) (Box 37, Folder 12)
    - Trial Material--Expert witnesses (Box 38, Folder 1)
    - Trial Material--Expert witnesses (Box 38, Folder 2)
    - Trial Material--Expert witnesses (Box 38, Folder 3)
    - Trial Material--Faculty & Staff handbook, 1970, 1976 (Box 38, Folder 4)
    - Trial Material--Faculty handbook (Box 38, Folder 5)
    - Trial Material--Faculty handbook & position vacancy, 1976 (Box 38, Folder 6)
    - Trial Material--Filing of suit (Box 38, Folder 7)
    - Trial Material--Filing of suit (Box 38, Folder 8)
    - Trial Material--Filing of suit (Box 39, Folder 1)
    - Trial Material--Graduate Committee work (Box 39, Folder 2)
    - Trial Material--Hapgood, Bob--Ford Foundation Grant (Box 39, Folder 3)
    - Trial Material--Lentz/Szanto material (Box 39, Folder 4)
    - Trial Material--Lindberg, Gary, 1975 (Box 39, Folder 5)
    - Trial Material--Materials related to teaching, Fall, 1974 (Box 39, Folder 6)
    - Trial Material--Murray, Don, 1977-1979 (Box 39, Folder 7)
    - Trial Material--Papers, 1978 (Box 39, Folder 8)
    - Trial Material--"MLA" book submission, 1976 (Box 39, Folder 9)
    - Trial Material--New Hampshire Commission (Box 39, Folder 10)
    - Trial Material--Plaintiff Exhibits (Box 39, Folder 11)
    - Trial Material--Petition (Box 40, Folder 1)
    - Trial Material--Related Cases & Decisions (Box 40, Folder 2)
    - Trial Material--Related Cases & Decisions--academic litigation (Box 40, Folder 3)
    - Trial Material--Related Cases & Decisions (Box 40, Folder 4)
    - Trial Material--Salary Standards (Box 40, Folder 5)
    - Trial Material--Schibanoff, Sue, 1978 (Box 40, Folder 6)
    - Trial Material--Settlement (Box 40, Folder 7)
    - Trial Material--Smith, Mark, 1979 (Box 40, Folder 8)
    - Trial Material--Spitz, Alan, 1978 (Box 40, Folder 9)
    - Trial Material--Spitz, Alan, 1979 (Box 40, Folder 10)
    - Trial Material--Talks (Box 41, Folder 1)
    - Trial Material (Box 41, Folder 2)
    - Trial Material (Box 41, Folder 3)
    - Trial Material-- (Box 41, Folder 4)
    - Trial Material--UNH and Annual Economic Welfare Report, 1978 (Box 41, Folder 5)
    - Trial Material--UNH Status on Women Report (Box 41, Folder 6)
    - Trial Material--Status on Women Report (Box 41, Folder 7)
    - Trial Material--University of British Columbia, 1972-1973 (Box 41, Folder 8)
    - Trial Material--University of British Columbia, 1972-1973 (Box 41, Folder 9)
    - Trial Material--University of British Columbia, 1980 (Box 41, Folder 10)
    - Trial Material--Witnesses & Informants (Box 42, Folder 1)
    - Trial Material--Warren Brown Affair, 1974-1975 (Box 42, Folder 2)
    - Trial Material--Warren Brown Affair, 1978 (Box 42, Folder 3)
    - Trial Material--Warren Brown Affair, 1978-1979 (Box 42, Folder 4)
    - Trial Material--Warren Brown Affair, 1979 (Box 42, Folder 5)
    - Trial Material--Women's Award dinner, 1978 (Box 42, Folder 6)
    - Trial Material--Women's Rights (Box 42, Folder 7)
    - Trial Material--Women's Rights (Box 42, Folder 8)
    - Trial Material--Women's Rights (Box 42, Folder 9)
    - Trial Material--Women's' Studies, 1975 (Box 42, Folder 10)
    - Trial Material--Women's Studies (Box 42, Folder 11)
    - Trial Material--Yale Faculty Records, August-December, 1968 (Box 42, Folder 12)
    - Trial Material--Yale Faculty Records, January-November, 1969 (Box 42, Folder 13)
    - Trial Material--Yale Faculty Records, 1970 (Box 42, Folder 14)
    - Trial Material--Yale Faculty Records, 1978 (Box 42, Folder 15)
    - Trial Material--Yale Faculty Records, 1979 (Box 42, Folder 16)
    - Miscellaneous research files [Added January, 2004], 1968- [ongoing] (Box 43, Folder [none])